Inventory of the A.G. Setter Photographs, 1918-1922
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
A.G. Setter photographs
1918-1922
Setter, A.G. (Alonzo G.)
00778
.10 cubic ft. (1 container)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Photographs of the New York Oil Company's operations in Salt Creek, Poison Spider, Iron Creek, and other oil fields in Wyoming between 1918 and 1922.
Biography of A.G. Setter
A.G. (Alonzo G.) Setter was vice president and later president of the New York Oil Company, which operated oil wells in Wyoming. Setter resided in Cattaraugus, New York.
Scope and Content
The A.G. Setter collection includes photographs of the Salt Creek, Poison Spider, and Iron Creek oil fields in Wyoming. There are also photographs of New York Oil Company properties and officers and a letter from Setter concerning a stock purchase dated 1918.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by A.G. Setter at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
This material was received from C.P. Setter in 1960.
Access Terms
New York Oil Company; Petroleum industry and trade -- Wyoming; Oil wells -- Wyoming; Oil fields -- Wyoming; Natrona County (Wyo.); Wyoming -- History -- 1890-1918; Wyoming -- History -- 1919-1945
Agriculture and Natural Resources; Mines and Mineral Resources; Business, Industry, Labor, and Commerce; Energy Production; Wyoming; Photographs
Container List
- Letter: A.G. Setter to Sam Cohen, concerning purchase of stock, 1918 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Hamilton Dome (Wyo.), 1918 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Iron Creek Oil Field:, 1918 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Midwest Refinery (Casper, Wyo.), 1919 (Box 1)
- Photographs: New York Oil Company Properties, 1918-1922 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Poison Spider Oil Field, 1919, 1921 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Salt Creek Oil Field, 1918-1919 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Setter, A.G., circa 1918 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Spindle Top #3 (Box 1)
- Photographs: Young, Minal, 1919 (Box 1)